{
    "subject": "resource/Someone_to_Watch_Over_Me_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1980s_crime_thriller_films",
    "human_readable": "Someone to Watch Over Me (film) is a 1980s crime thriller film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8505565524101257,
            "question": "Is 'Someone to Watch Over Me' a comedy or a thriller?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709230780601501,
            "question": "Was 'Someone to Watch Over Me' a critically acclaimed film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6368488073348999,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Someone to Watch Over Me'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5940402746200562,
            "question": "How was the film 'Someone to Watch Over Me' received by audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5385380387306213,
            "question": "What makes 'Someone to Watch Over Me' a memorable film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.53661048412323,
            "question": "Can you describe the plot of 'Someone to Watch Over Me'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.535462498664856,
            "question": "Are there any similar films to 'Someone to Watch Over Me'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5070640444755554,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in 'Someone to Watch Over Me'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5023053884506226,
            "question": "What decade was the film 'Someone to Watch Over Me' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43447810411453247,
            "question": "What themes are explored in 'Someone to Watch Over Me'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Someone to Watch Over Me (film) is a 1980s crime thriller film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4831_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What decade was the film 'Someone to Watch Over Me' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4831_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the actors in 'Someone to Watch Over Me'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4831_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any similar films to 'Someone to Watch Over Me'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4831_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4831_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Someone to Watch Over Me\" is a 1987 neo-noir romantic thriller film, and also describe it as a \"moody, seductive crime thriller\". These statements suggest that the film is indeed a crime thriller from the 1980s."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain multiple references that support the statement \"Someone to Watch Over Me (film) is a 1980s crime thriller film.\" Specifically, several documents mention that it is a crime thriller from 1987, which falls within the 1980s."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}